New England Medical Center Records MS099
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Finance records, 1935 -- 1989; MS099.006; 60.0 Linear Feet; 2 Volumes
  - Financial ledgers, 1935 -- 1980; MS099.006.008; 32.4 Linear Feet; 2 Volumes
    - Voucher register, 1959-10 -- 1960-09; MS099.006.008.279.00001 (Box 279)
    - Financial ledger, 1950 -- 1954; MS099.006.008.280.00001 (Box 280)
    - Financial ledger, 1955 -- 1956; MS099.006.008.281.00001 (Box 281)
    - Cash control sheets, 1953-03 -- 1953-05; MS099.006.008.282.00001 (Box 282)
    - Cash control sheets, 1953 -- 1959; MS099.006.008.283.00001 (Box 283)
    - Cash control sheets, 1956 -- 1959; MS099.006.008.284.00001 (Box 284)
    - Hospital and clinic income summary, 1953-12 -- 1954-10; MS099.006.008.285.00001 (Box 285)
    - Hospital and clinic income summary, 1954 -- 1955; MS099.006.008.286.00001 (Box 286)
    - Voucher register and cash receipts, 1951 -- 1954; MS099.006.008.301.00001 (Box 301)
    - Voucher register and cash receipts, 1955 -- 1961; MS099.006.008.316.00001 (Box 316)
    - Voucher register and cash receipts, 1955-02 -- 1956-02; MS099.006.008.316.00002 (Box 316)
    - Cash receipts, 1955 -- 1956; MS099.006.008.317.00001 (Box 317)
    - House and clinic income, 1956-10-01 -- 1957-09-30; MS099.006.008.317.00002 (Box 317)
    - Cash receipts, 1958-10 -- 1959-09; MS099.006.008.318.00001 (Box 318)
    - Financial ledger, 1955 -- 1957; MS099.006.008.318.00002 (Box 318)
    - Financial ledger, 1952 -- 1955; MS099.006.008.318.00003 (Box 318)
    - Financial ledger, 1959 -- 1960; MS099.006.008.323.00001 (Box 323)
    - Financial ledger, 1955 -- 1965; MS099.006.008.323.00002 (Box 323)
    - Cash receipts, 1956 -- 1959; MS099.006.008.325.00001 (Box data_value_missing_4dfa580b3ce99882fdef2d972c918409)
    - Hospital and clinic income summary, 1955 -- 1956; MS099.006.008.325.00002 (Box data_value_missing_4dfa580b3ce99882fdef2d972c918409)
- Development office records, 1969 -- 1986; MS099.007; 4.8 Linear Feet
  This series contains correspondence, reports, financial statements, audits, and a sampling of individual donor records regarding fund raising and planning for the expansion of NEMC.
  According to Dave Nathan's Guide to the NEMC Archives, the follow items are missing:Reports; Correspondence, 1976-1978; and Correspondence re: legacies, 1965-1980.
  The original order created by the NEMC archives has been maintained.
  - Auditors working papers and Development office statistical reports, 1974 -- 1979; MS099.007.163b (Box 163)
  - Development office statistical reports, 1974 -- 1979; MS099.007.164a (Box 164)
  - Board of Trustees - minutes and overseers list, 1983 -- 1984; MS099.007.164b.00001 (Box 164)
  - Bylaws - mechanical finance, 1985; MS099.007.164b.00002 (Box 164)
  - Finance, 1984 -- 1985; MS099.007.164b.00003 (Box 164)
  - Board of Governors, 1984 -- 1985; MS099.007.164b.00004 (Box 164)
  - Overseer involvement, 1985; MS099.007.164b.00005 (Box 164)
  - Executive committee, 1985; MS099.007.164b.00006 (Box 164)
  - Community practice, 1984 -- 1985; MS099.007.164b.00007 (Box 164)
  - Board of Governors meeting, 1984; MS099.007.164b.00008 (Box 164)
  - Board of Governors Nominating Committee, 1980 -- 1981; MS099.007.164b.00009 (Box 164)
  - Nominating Committee, 1982 -- 1983; MS099.007.164b.00010 (Box 164)
  - Nominating Committee, 1984; MS099.007.164b.00011 (Box 164)
  - Nominating Committee, 1985; MS099.007.164b.00012 (Box 164)
  - Ladies Committee, 1982 -- 1985; MS099.007.164b.00013 (Box 164)
  - Kiwanis Trauma Institute, 1984 -- 1985; MS099.007.164b.00014 (Box 164)
  - Conflict of interest statements, 1983; MS099.007.164b.00015 (Box 164)
  - Real Estate Committee overseer involvement, 1985; MS099.007.164b.00016 (Box 164)
  - Annual meeting originals, 1985; MS099.007.164b.00017 (Box 164)
  - Annual meeting script, 1985; MS099.007.164b.00018 (Box 164)
  - Annual meeting signage, 1985; MS099.007.164b.00019 (Box 164)
  - Annual meeting attendees, 1985; MS099.007.164b.00020 (Box 164)
  - Jerome Grossman's speech, 1984; MS099.007.164b.00021; Grossman, Jerome (Box 164)
  - Listings of committees and overseer's addresses, 1984; MS099.007.164b.00022 (Box 164)
  - Annual meeting bills, 1986; MS099.007.164b.00023 (Box 164)
  - Tufts University and New England Medical Center Facilities Master Plan, 1982-1992, MS099.007.164b.00024 (Box 164)
  - Letter from Larry Smith regarding 1986 annual meeting, MS099.007.164b.00025; Smith, Larry L. (Box 164)
  - Annual meeting historical file, 1985; MS099.007.164b.00026 (Box 164)
  - Annual meeting, 1985; MS099.007.164b.00027 (Box 164)
  - Annual meeting booklet, 1984; MS099.007.165.00001 (Box 165)
  - Annual meeting booklet, 1983; MS099.007.165.00002 (Box 165)
  - Bylaws, 1983; MS099.007.165.00003 (Box 165)
  - Corporate reorganization, 1983; MS099.007.165.00004 (Box 165)
  - Trustees questionnaires, 1983; MS099.007.165.00005 (Box 165)
  - Annual meeting expenses, 1985; MS099.007.165.00006 (Box 165)
  - Job descriptions, 1983; MS099.007.165.00007 (Box 165)
  - Chinese visitors expenses, 1984; MS099.007.165.00008 (Box 165)
  - Nichols and Stone Furniture Company, 1983; MS099.007.165.00009 (Box 165)
  - Annual meeting, 1985; MS099.007.165.00010 (Box 165)
  - Board of Governors and Trustees listings, 1982 -- 1983; MS099.007.165.00011 (Box 165)
  - The News in Review, 1985; MS099.007.165.00012; New England Medical Center (Box 165)
  - NEMCH fund, financial, 1969 -- 1976; MS099.007.165.00013 (Box 165)
  - Building fund scrapbook of forms and other publications, 1967 -- 1968; MS099.007.165.00014 (Box 165)
  - Blueprint for the future, 1964; MS099.007.165.00015; Tufts University School of Dental Medicine (Box 165)
  - Observations and recommendations on the organization and the program of NEMC, 1958; MS099.007.165.00016; Hinsey, Joseph C. (Box 165)
  - Financial statements, 1977 -- 1978; MS099.007.165.00017 (Box 165)
  - Payroll distributions, 1971 -- 1972; MS099.007.165.00018 (Box 165)
  - Correspondence, 1956; MS099.007.165.00019 (Box 165)
  - The Health Fund for Medical Care, Education, and Research, 1960 -- 1970; MS099.007.165.00020; Gummere, Francis B. (Box 165)
  - Sampling of donations, 1967 -- 1979; MS099.007.165.00021 (Box 165)
  - Affiliation agreement revision, 1946; MS099.007.165.00022 (Box 165)
  - Endowment fund, 1967 -- 1979; MS099.007.165.00023 (Box 165)
  - Appreciation Day, 1974; MS099.007.165.00024 (Box 165)
  - Cumulative individual contributor records, samples, 1969 -- 1979; MS099.007.311.00001 (Box MS099 Shared 4)
  - Subscription records, samples, 1975 -- 1978; MS099.007.311.00002 (Box MS099 Shared 4)
  - NEMCH Building Fund, 1974 -- 1975; MS099.007.311.00003 (Box MS099 Shared 4)
  - Subscription records, samples, 1967 -- 1970; MS099.007.311.00004 (Box MS099 Shared 4)
  - Subscription records, samples, 1970 -- 1974; MS099.007.311.00005 (Box MS099 Shared 4)
  - NEMCH research and suspense accounts, 1974 -- 1975; MS099.007.311.00006 (Box MS099 Shared 4)
  - NEMCH Building Fund, 1976 -- 1977; MS099.007.311.00007 (Box MS099 Shared 4)
  - Fall appeal, 1978 -- 1979; MS099.007.311.00008 (Box MS099 Shared 4)
  - Documentation for auditors, 1979 -- 1980; MS099.007.311.00009 (Box MS099 Shared 4)
- Legal counsel records, 1946 -- 1975; MS099.008; 12.0 Linear Feet
  This series contains correspondence, memoranda, meeting minutes, confidential reports, financial and tax records, contracts, abstracts of titles, court papers, estate records, wills, and property transactions. These documents were created by the law firm Ropes & Gray, which served as legal counsel for NEMC and its predecessor institutions.
  This series has been arranged into 3 sub-series: Boston Dispensary; Boston Floating Hospital; and Pratt Clinic/New England Center Hospital. This series is arranged chronologically within each sub-series.
  - Boston Dispensary, 1953 -- 1963; MS099.008.001; 1 Volumes
    This sub-series contains property transactions and wills.
    - Property transactions, Rehabilitation Center, 1956 -- 1963; MS099.008.001.166.00001 (Box 166)
    - Wills, Estate of John F. MacCana, 1953 -- 1954; MS099.008.001.166.00002 (Box 166)
  - Boston Floating Hospital, 1957 -- 1965; 1957 -- 1962; MS099.008.002; 1 Volumes
    This series contains files of property transactions and pension plans.
    - General matters (1 of 3), 1959 -- 1965; MS099.008.002.166.00003 (Box 166)
    - General matters (2 of 3), 1959 -- 1965; MS099.008.002.166.00004 (Box 166)
    - General matters (3 of 3), 1959 -- 1965; MS099.008.002.166.00005 (Box 166)
    - Pension plan, 1959 -- 1961; MS099.008.002.166.00006 (Box 166)
    - Property transactions, 15 Nassau Street, 1957; MS099.008.002.166.00007 (Box 166)
    - Property transactions, Ash Street, 1958; MS099.008.002.166.00008 (Box 166)
    - Property transactions, 9 Nassau Street, 1958; MS099.008.002.166.00009 (Box 166)
    - Property transactions, 11 Nassau Street, 1958; MS099.008.002.166.00010 (Box 166)
    - Property transactions, 24 Oak Street, 1961; MS099.008.002.166.00011 (Box 166)
    - Property transactions, 11-13 Nassau Street, 1958; MS099.008.002.166.00012 (Box 166)
  - Pratt Clinic/New England Center Hospital, 1946 -- 1975; 1946 -- 1967; MS099.008.003; 1 Volumes
    This sub-series contains tax abatements and property transactions.
    - Organization of surgical hospital (1 of 3), 1948; MS099.008.003.167.00001 (Box 167)
    - Organization of surgical hospital (2 of 3), 1948; MS099.008.003.167.00002 (Box 167)
    - Organization of surgical hospital (3 of 3), 1948; MS099.008.003.167.00003 (Box 167)
    - University Anesthetists Corporation, 1958; MS099.008.003.167.00004 (Box 167)
    - Bingham Associates Fund of Massachusetts, miscellaneous (1 of 3), 1948; MS099.008.003.167.00005 (Box 167)
      Article of organization, name change.
    - Bingham Associates Fund of Massachusetts, miscellaneous (2 of 3), 1948; MS099.008.003.167.00006 (Box 167)
    - Bingham Associates Fund of Massachusetts, miscellaneous (3 of 3), 1948; MS099.008.003.167.00007 (Box 167)
    - Bingham Associates Fund of Massachusetts, miscellaneous matters (1 of 2), 1950; MS099.008.003.167.00008 (Box 167)
    - Bingham Associates Fund of Massachusetts, miscellaneous matters (2 of 2), 1950; MS099.008.003.167.00009 (Box 167)
    - New England Center Hospital, miscellaneous, 1951; MS099.008.003.168.00001 (Box 168)
      Plans and blue prints.
    - New England Center Hospital, miscellaneous, 1951; MS099.008.003.168.00002 (Box 168)
    - New England Center Hospital, miscellaneous, 1951; MS099.008.003.168.00003 (Box 168)
    - New England Center Hospital, miscellaneous, 1952; MS099.008.003.168.00004 (Box 168)
    - New England Center Hospital, miscellaneous, 1953; MS099.008.003.168.00005 (Box 168)
      Attorney agreement, insurance, plans, and blue prints.
    - New England Center Hospital, miscellaneous, 1953; MS099.008.003.168.00006 (Box 168)
    - New England Center Hospital, miscellaneous matters, 1954; MS099.008.003.169.00001 (Box 169)
      Letter to, and response from, senior surgeon.
    - New England Center Hospital, miscellaneous matters, 1954; MS099.008.003.169.00002 (Box 169)
    - New England Center Hospital, miscellaneous matters, 1955; MS099.008.003.169.00003 (Box 169)
      Will and estate of William Bingham 2nd.
    - New England Center Hospital, miscellaneous, 1955; MS099.008.003.169.00004 (Box 169)
    - New England Center Hospital, miscellaneous matters, 1956; MS099.008.003.170.00001 (Box 170)
    - New England Center Hospital, miscellaneous matters, 1956; MS099.008.003.170.00002 (Box 170)
    - New England Center Hospital, miscellaneous matters, 1957; MS099.008.003.170.00003 (Box 170)
    - New England Center Hospital, miscellaneous matters, 1957; MS099.008.003.170.00004 (Box 170)
    - New England Center Hospital, miscellaneous matters, 1958; MS099.008.003.170.00005 (Box 170)
      Hower Committee report.
    - New England Center Hospital, miscellaneous, 1958; MS099.008.003.171.00001 (Box 171)
      Lease to Rockford Furniture Company Inc., Research Activities Report
    - New England Center Hospital, miscellaneous matters, 1959; MS099.008.003.171.00002 (Box 171)
    - New England Center Hospital, miscellaneous matters, 1960; MS099.008.003.171.00003 (Box 171)
    - New England Center Hospital, miscellaneous matters, 1961; MS099.008.003.171.00004 (Box 171)
    - New England Center Hospital, miscellaneous matters, 1961; MS099.008.003.171.00005 (Box 171)
    - New England Center Hospital, treasurer's account, 1964; MS099.008.003.172.00001 (Box 172)
      Insurance survey and recommendations.
    - New England Center Hospital, miscellaneous matters, 1963; MS099.008.003.172.00002 (Box 172)
      Estate of Raphael T. Genoves.
    - New England Center Hospital, miscellaneous matters, 1963; MS099.008.003.172.00003 (Box 172)
    - New England Center Hospital, miscellaneous matters, 1964; MS099.008.003.172.00004 (Box 172)
    - New England Center Hospital, miscellaneous matters, 1963; MS099.008.003.172.00005 (Box 172)
    - New England Center Hospital, treasurer's account, 1964; MS099.008.003.172.00006 (Box 172)
      Treasurer's account receipts.
    - New England Center Hospital, miscellaneous matters, 1964; MS099.008.003.172.00007 (Box 172)
      Receipts, refund claims.
    - New England Center Hospital, miscellaneous matters, 1964; MS099.008.003.173.00001 (Box 173)
    - New England Center Hospital, treasurer's account, 1965; MS099.008.003.173.00002 (Box 173)
    - New England Center Hospital, miscellaneous matters, 1965; MS099.008.003.173.00003 (Box 173)
      Corporation Consolidation Report.
    - New England Center Hospital Bank borrowings, 1946 -- 1952; MS099.008.003.173.00004 (Box 173)
    - New England Center HospitalLease to Brown Furniture Company, Inc., 1965; MS099.008.003.173.00005 (Box 173)
    - New England Center Hospital, contracts and law memoranda (1 of 2), 1947 -- 1960; MS099.008.003.173.00006 (Box 173)
    - New England Center Hospital, contracts and law memoranda (2 of 2), 1947 -- 1960; MS099.008.003.173.00007 (Box 173)
    - New England Center Hospital, miscellaneous staff matters, 1960 -- 1962; MS099.008.003.173.00008 (Box 173)
    - New England Center Hospital, NEMC relations, 1960 -- 1965; MS099.008.003.173.00009 (Box 173)
    - New England Center Hospital, retirement plan for staff, 1960 -- 1964; MS099.008.003.173.00010 (Box 173)
    - New England Center Hospital, staff by-laws, 1953 -- 1962; MS099.008.003.173.00011 (Box 173)
    - Sale of Dore, Dillaway, Hollis, Washington, and Tremont streets (1 of 8), 1962; MS099.008.003.173.00012 (Box 173)
    - Sale of Dore, Dillaway, Hollis, Washington, and Tremont streets (2 of 8), 1962; MS099.008.003.174.00001 (Box 174)
    - Sale of Dore, Dillaway, Hollis, Washington, and Tremont streets (3 of 8), 1962; MS099.008.003.174.00002 (Box 174)
    - Sale of Dore, Dillaway, Hollis, Washington, and Tremont streets (4 of 8), 1962; MS099.008.003.174.00003 (Box 174)
    - Sale of Dore, Dillaway, Hollis, Washington, and Tremont streets (5 of 8), 1962; MS099.008.003.174.00004 (Box 174)
    - Sale of Dore, Dillaway, Hollis, Washington, and Tremont streets (6 of 8), 1962; MS099.008.003.174.00005 (Box 174)
    - Sale of Dore, Dillaway, Hollis, Washington, and Tremont streets (7 of 8), 1962; MS099.008.003.174.00006 (Box 174)
    - Sale of Dore, Dillaway, Hollis, Washington, and Tremont streets (8 of 8), 1962; MS099.008.003.174.00007 (Box 174)
    - Lease of Metropolitan Theatre (1 of 2), 1959 -- 1969; MS099.008.003.174.00008 (Box 174)
    - Lease of Metropolitan Theatre (2 of 2), 1959 -- 1969; MS099.008.003.174.00009 (Box 174)
    - Tupper gift, 1964 -- 1975; MS099.008.003.174.00010 (Box 174)
    - Bingham Associates Fund of Massachusetts, tax abatement, Harrison Avenue, 1947; MS099.008.003.174.00011 (Box 174)
    - New England Center Hospital, federal tax status of certain grants, 1961 -- 1963; MS099.008.003.174.00012 (Box 174)
    - New England Center Hospital, federal tax status of certain grants, 1961 -- 1963; MS099.008.003.174.00013 (Box 174)
    - New England Center Hospital, application for tax abatement of real estate on 4-16 Bennet street, 1953; MS099.008.003.175.00001 (Box 175)
    - New England Center Hospital, application for tax abatement of real estate on 4-16 Bennet street, 1954; MS099.008.003.175.00002 (Box 175)
    - New England Center Hospital, application for tax abatement of real estate on 744-756 Washington street, 1954; MS099.008.003.175.00003 (Box 175)
    - New England Center Hospital, application for tax abatement of taxes and for statutory exemption, 1955; MS099.008.003.175.00004 (Box 175)
    - New England Center Hospital, application for tax abatement of taxes and for statutory exemption, 1956; MS099.008.003.175.00005 (Box 175)
    - New England Center Hospital, application for tax abatement of taxes and for statutory exemption, 1957; MS099.008.003.175.00006 (Box 175)
    - New England Center Hospital, application for tax abatement of \real estate taxes, 1958; MS099.008.003.175.00007 (Box 175)
    - New England Center Hospital, application for tax abatement of real estate taxes, 1959; MS099.008.003.175.00008 (Box 175)
    - New England Center Hospital, application for tax abatement of real estate taxes, 1963; MS099.008.003.175.00009 (Box 175)
    - New England Center Hospital, application for tax abatement of real estate taxes, 1964; MS099.008.003.175.00010 (Box 175)
    - New England Center Hospital, tax exemption on Ziskind building, 1953 -- 1955; MS099.008.003.175.00011 (Box 175)
    - New England Center Hospital, petition for statutory exemption and application for abatement covering Bond building, 1961; MS099.008.003.175.00012 (Box 175)
    - New England Center Hospital, estate of Paul Parra, 1952; MS099.008.003.175.00013 (Box 175)
    - New England Center Hospital, will of Francis P. Magann, 1961 -- 1963; MS099.008.003.175.00014 (Box 175)
    - Bingham Associates Fund of Massachusetts, Willians vs. MGH services and Joseph Pratt Diagnostic Hospital, 1950; MS099.008.003.175.00015 (Box 175)
    - New England Center Hospital, Kogan vs. Okum, 1958; MS099.008.003.175.00016 (Box 175)
    - New England Center Hospital, Maier vs. Etsten et al, 1961 -- 1965; MS099.008.003.175.00017 (Box 175)
    - Bingham Associates Fund of Massachusetts, Ford building, 1948; MS099.008.003.175.00018 (Box 175)
    - Bingham Associates Fund of Massachusetts, NECH partial purchase of real estate, 1950; MS099.008.003.175.00019 (Box 175)
    - New England Center Hospital, Harrison avenue and Tyler street properties, 1952; MS099.008.003.175.00020 (Box 175)
    - New England Center Hospital, acquisition of Bennet street property, 1953; MS099.008.003.175.00021 (Box 175)
    - Ford Manufacturing, Inc. to NECH, 13-25 Harvard street, 1952; MS099.008.003.175.00022 (Box 175)
    - New England Center Hospital, purchase of Osgood building, 1954; MS099.008.003.175.00023 (Box 175)
    - New England Center Hospital, acquisition of 13-15 Harvard street, 1953; MS099.008.003.175.00024 (Box 175)
    - New England Center Hospital, purchase of 174 Harrison avenue, 1955; MS099.008.003.175.00025 (Box 175)
    - New England Center Hospital, sale of Bond building, 1955; MS099.008.003.175.00026 (Box 175)
    - New England Center Hospital, Metropolitan Theatre properties (1 of 2), 1962 -- 1967; MS099.008.003.175.00027 (Box 175)
    - New England Center Hospital, Metropolitan Theatre properties (2 of 2), 1962 -- 1967; MS099.008.003.175.00028 (Box 175)
- Corporate Public Affairs office records, 1927 -- 1997; MS099.009; 26.4 Linear Feet
  This series contains the files of the Office of Corporate Public Affairs, which was formed in 1982 to provide public relations, marketing, and publication design services to NEMC. Files include press releases, press clippings, publications produced by or for the office, and press scrapbooks documenting NEMC activities, events, and facilities. Also included in this series is information about the China Exchange Program under the stewardship of Judith Kurland, which brought Chinese physicians to NEMC.
  Photographs are located in the Photographs and audiovisual material series (MS099.001). Case files compiled by the office on individuals affiliated with NEMC are located in the Personnel records series (MS099.005).
  According to Dave Nathan's Guide to the NEMC Archives, the following items are missing: 1 volume of the Boston Dispensary scrapbooks; and Video news clippings, 1986-1988, news program interviews with NEMC physicians (56 VHS cassettes).
  This series has been arranged into 4 sub-series: Scrapbooks; Publications; Subject files; and China Exchange Program. The original order created by the NEMC archives has been maintained.
  - Scrapbooks, 1927 -- 1956; 1927 -- 1981; MS099.009.001; 3.6 Linear Feet
    - Boston Dispensary, publicity, 1927-10 -- 1930-04; MS099.009.001.176.00001 (Box 176)
    - Boston Dispensary, publicity, 1930-04 -- 1933-01; MS099.009.001.176.00002 (Box 176)
    - Boston Dispensary, 1933-01 -- 1934-08; MS099.009.001.176.00003 (Box 176)
    - Boston Dispensary, 1934-09-02 -- 1935-09-15; MS099.009.001.176.00004 (Box 176)
    - Boston Dispensary, 1935-02-15 -- 1937-07-09; MS099.009.001.176.00005 (Box 176)
    - Boston Dispensary, 1937-07-09 -- 1940-02-01; MS099.009.001.177.00001 (Box 177)
    - Boston Floating Hospital, publicity, 1948-10 -- 1955; MS099.009.001.177.00002 (Box 177)
    - Boston Dispensary, 1940-02-01 -- 1942-12-31; MS099.009.001.177.00003 (Box 177)
    - Boston Dispensary, publicity, 1943 -- 1948-03; MS099.009.001.177.00004 (Box 177)
    - New England Center Hospital, 1948 -- 1952-05; MS099.009.001.177.00005 (Box 177)
    - New England Center Hospital, 1950-01 -- 1953-01; MS099.009.001.178.00001 (Box 178)
    - New England Center Hospital, publicity, 1952-05 -- 1954; MS099.009.001.178.00002 (Box 178)
    - Boston Dispensary/New England Center Hospital, publicity, 1953-02 -- 1955-06; MS099.009.001.178.00003 (Box 178)
    - PC/NECH, Grand Rounds, 1956; MS099.009.001.178.00004 (Box 178)
  - Publications, 1939 -- 1997; 1939 -- 1963; MS099.009.002; 18.0 Linear Feet
    - Tufts Folia Medica, 1939 -- 1963; MS099.009.002.179 (Box 179)
      Tufts Folia Medica was formerly New England Medical Center Bulletin (1939-1954) and Tufts-New England Medical Center Bulletin (1955-1960).
      New England Medical Center
    - T-NEMC Times, 1974 -- 1981; MS099.009.002.180 (Box 180)
      Tufts-New England Medical Center
    - Press clippings related to NEMC (1 of 3), 1988; MS099.009.002.311.00010 (Box MS099 Shared 4)
    - Press clippings related to NEMC (2 of 3), 1987 -- 1988; MS099.009.002.311.00011 (Box MS099 Shared 4)
    - Press clippings related to NEMC (3 of 3), 1982 -- 1987; MS099.009.002.311.00012 (Box MS099 Shared 4)
    - Press releases, 1986; MS099.009.002.311.00013 (Box MS099 Shared 4)
    - In the News, 1988 -- 1989; MS099.009.002.311.00014 (Box MS099 Shared 4)
    - News releases, 1982; MS099.009.002.311.00015 (Box 311)
    - News releases, 1983; MS099.009.002.311.00016 (Box 311)
    - News releases, 1984; MS099.009.002.311.00017 (Box 311)
    - News releases, 1985; MS099.009.002.311.00018 (Box 311)
    - All That Jazz, 1985 -- 1986; MS099.009.002.315.00001 (Box 315)
    - NEMC Quarterly, 1995 -- 1997; MS099.009.002.315.00002 (Box 315)
    - T-NEMC News, 1964 -- 1978; MS099.009.002.315.00003 (Box 315)
    - T-NEMC News, 1965 -- 1969; MS099.009.002.315.00004 (Box 315)
    - T-NEMC Times, 1974 -- 1977; MS099.009.002.315.00005 (Box 315)
    - The Reporter mock-ups, 1990; MS099.009.002.315.00006 (Box 315)
  - Subject files, 1959 -- 1990; MS099.009.003; 2.4 Linear Feet
    This sub-series contains publicity files concerning the activities, events, and facilities produced by the office of Corporate Public Affairs.
    - Bay Cove Human Services, 1973 -- 1974; MS099.009.003.181.00001 (Box 181)